https://barbaracarrellas.com/privacy-policy/

HomeBarbara CarrellasBackAbout Barbara CarrellasTestimonialsUn-BlogContactPrivacy PolicyWorkshops/EventsBackUpcoming EventsWorkshopsBackOrgasms with SpiritSex & SpiritualityUrban TantraBackUrban Tantra® ExperienceUrban Tantra® Professional Training ProgramColleges and UniversitiesCorporate WorkshopsOnline Sex ClassesSex/Life CoachingRead/Watch/ListenBackBooks & MP3sBackUrban Tantra: Sacred Sex for the Twenty-First CenturyEcstasy is Necessary: A Practical Guide to Sex, Relationships and Oh So Much MoreLuxurious LovingBreath and Energy Orgasms: A Guided MeditationMeeting Your Inner LoverHow To Become A Sexual HealerTranscendent BodiesMediaBackVideoPodcasts & RadioLinks & Resources
E-mail: info@urbantantra.org
What personal information do we collect from the people who visit our website?When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:• To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
• To quickly process your transactions.
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.Do we use ‘cookies’?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to:• Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.Use Of Web Beacons Or GIF FilesWeb pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons—sometimes also called single-pixel gifs—that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.Some of these web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. We prohibit web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We have technological and operational security policies and procedures in place to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration or unintentional destruction. Our personnel who have access to the data have been trained to maintain the confidentiality of such information. We may release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Links To Other Web SitesThis privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.Additional EU DisclosuresOur role as data controller and data processor: Barbara Carrellas/Urban Tantra® generally acts as the data controller of your information submitted through our website.If you are situated in the EU and have any complaints regarding our privacy practices as data controller, you have the right to make a complaint at any time to your local Supervisory Authority. We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach your Supervisory Authority so please contact us first. If you are situated in the EU and have a complaint, please contact our privacy manager at info@urbantantra.org.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at info@urbantantra.org.• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from all correspondence.Changes To This StatementWe have the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the bottom of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.barbaracarrellas.com
POB 415
New York, NY 10108
USA
info@urbantantra.org
Updated on 11 June 2018
FREE GIFT! Name:* E-mail:* Would you like to subscribe to our mailing list? (Y/N): Verification:SubmitResetP.S. Want to be considered for a place on Barbara’s Resource Guide? Send us a message and let us know.
CLOSE
Free Gift Name:* E-mail:* Would you like to subscribe to our mailing list? (Y/N): Verification:SubmitReset
CLOSE
